http://www.intonation.co.uk/en/privacy-policy

TranslationStep-By-Step GuideAerospace & DefenceBusiness CardE-LearningWebsite LocalisationLegal Translation ServicesManufacturing & EngineeringMarket ResearchMedicalPatentPharmaceuticalSportsTechnical TranslationTranscreationTranscriptionEnglishForeignFor Transcribed DocumentsInterpretingBusinessConferenceLegalRemoteOther ServicesDesign & Web Agency ServicesForeign Language SEOLanguage TrainingProofreadingSubtitling ServicesTypesetting & Desktop PublishingVoiceover ServicesCase StudiesAboutJoin the TeamCase StudiesWhy Choose Intonation?Covid-19 UpdateNewsContact
PRIVACY POLICY
Protecting your privacy
Your privacy is important to us. Intonation Ltd. is committed to safeguarding the personal information you provide to us and to protecting your privacy, as well as clearly stating how that information is used to deliver our service to you.
The purpose of this privacy statement is to assist you in understanding how Intonation Ltd. uses personal information collected via this website, and the choices you can make about how your personal information is used.
Where we hold your information, we will notify you, by email, of any amendments to this privacy statement and provide you with details of what to do next.
The services offered by Intonation Ltd. are intended for persons over the age of 13. Users under the age of 13 are welcome to browse the Intonation website, but should not provide us with any personal information.
The information we collect
You do not have to provide any personal information in order to browse this website.
We may collect personal information about you when you register with us or use our quotation forms. This information includes your name, email
address and phone number.
In addition to your personal information, when you use our website, we may collect tracking information such as your IP address, browser type, the operating system you use, the name of your internet service provider and pages visited on the site.
Intonation Ltd. gets this information by using technologies, including cookies to increase the functionality and user-friendliness of our website and to better tailor our website to your needs. For example, we may want to know how long the average user spends on our website, or which pages get the most attention. Information such as this will only be used in aggregate form and will not identify you personally.
In order to send email communications to our registrants, we use a third-party email service provider. Data will be transferred to our email service provider for this purpose. Our email service provider is currently Campaign Monitor. We may, without notice, change our provider to one delivering similar services. Where this occurs, we will ensure that at least the same level of protection is applied to your personal information.
What Information do we collect
How the information is used
We collect information on our users to:
help us improve and provide a personalised service to you
conduct market research.
reply to your enquiries more efficiently through the services we provide.
run competitions.
inform you of new offers, products and services that may be of interest to you.
We also use information in aggregate form (i.e. your individual details cannot be identified) to:
build up marketing profiles.
aid strategic development.
audit usage of the site.
help us deliver relevant content to you on social media websites such as Facebook (see 'Online advertising we use').
Online advertising we use
Google analytics & re-marketing
Our websites use Google analytics and Google's re-marketing technology. This technology enables users who have already visited our online services and shown interest in our services to see targeted advertising on Google partner network websites. Likewise, users that are similar to the visitors of our websites can be addressed. The advertising will be displayed through the use of web cookies. Using cookies, the user behaviour on a website can be analysed and subsequently utilised to provide targeted product recommendations and advertising based on the user's interests.
If you would prefer to not receive any targeted advertising, you can deactivate the use of cookies for these purposes through Google. Alternatively, users can deactivate the use of cookies by third-party providers by visiting the
Network Advertising Initiative's deactivation website.
Please note that Google has its own data protection policy, which is independent of our own. We assume no responsibility or liability for their policies and procedures. Please read
Google's privacy policy before using our websites.
How Google uses data.
How we share information with third parties
We share information with trusted third parties, Intereurope Ltd., Intereurope Communications Group Ltd. and Tri-Synergy Marketing Ltd., to help us with advertising, marketing and promotions as well as analyse the effectiveness of campaigns and promotions.
We reserve the right to release personal information without your consent or without consulting you, when we believe that this is appropriate, such as to comply with our legal obligations, to enforce our terms and conditions or to protect the security of this website or to prevent fraud.
Our email service provider Campaign Monitor uses U.S. based data centres. Up to date information regarding Campaign Monitor and GDPR compliance can be found at: https://www.campaignmonitor.com/trust/gdpr-compliance/
Cookies and other similar technologies
Intonation Ltd. uses first-party and third-party, session and persistent cookies, tags and other similar technologies as a means of collecting non-sensitive information on general website usage so that we may improve your experience on our website.
Cookies are a small piece of information placed on your computer's hard drive via your web browser to enable the sender to identify, authenticate and maintain specific information about how users behave. Cookies make using the website's facilities quicker, easier and more convenient as well as allowing registered Intonation Ltd. users to be presented with a personalised version of the site.
For more information on the cookies used on this website and how to opt out of accepting cookies, see our list of cookies. Please read this information in full before deciding whether to disable cookies, as doing so may reduce your enjoyment of our website.
Links
This website contains links to other websites that are not controlled by Intonation Ltd. This privacy statement applies only to this website.
Requesting a copy of your personal information
You may, at any time, request a copy of the personal information we hold on you, free of charge. To do this, please contact us via email at info@intonation.co.uk. We will aim to respond within three working days and provide the information within 28 days.
Unsubscribing
You may unsubscribe from Intonation Ltd.’s emails by following the unsubscribe link in any of our email communications to you.
